# Fyn Starr

Email: fynstarr96@gmail.com (please email me for further contact details)

#### Personal Profile

I am a friendly person who has excellent customer service skills that have been developed over a wide range of customer facing roles, which allows me to remain focused and empathetic while remaining professional when dealing with customer complaints. I have extensive knowledge with computers and am able to learn most systems quickly and confidently. Being an organised person I am able to prioritise my work efficiently, completing tasks within deadlines and with a high attention to detail. From various work experience I have been able to develop my skills so that I am able to work well in a team and on my own.

### Education

- Information Technology, Distinction.
- Drama, B.
- Music, B.
- Certificate of Personal Effectiveness, Level 2/ B GCSE Equivalent.
- English, C.
- Maths, C.

#### Skills

- Customer Facing Engaging positively with customers in any situation.
- Quick Learner Learning new systems, ways of working, and policies.
- Practical I enjoy finding solutions to problems, and do so in a logical manner.
- Computer Literate I am very familiar with computers, and have used Windows and Linux operating systems for personal use for several years.

## Key Employment History

Capita | Hepworth House, Clay Pit Ln, Leeds LS2 8AE

Customer Service Advisor | November 2017 - June 2018

Vodafone | The White House, Melbourne St, LS2 7PS

Customer Service Advisor | January 2016 - July 2016

Milford | 170 Cardigan Rd, Leeds LS6 1LL

Yard Operator | April 2014 – July 2015